[Music]
we would like to thank FWD the official
insurer of the PBA to a growing PBA
family because of this collaboration we
feel protected
knowing that we are partnered with a
trusted insurance company that
encourages Filipinos to pursue their
passion and live life without hesitation
we're looking to strengthen our ties
with you in the future years again
welcome to the
[Music]
PBI thank you commissioner it's uh great
to be here tonight and FWD is delighted
to be the official insurer of the PBA
basketball is a national Pastime in the
Philippines
and FWD is truly excited to become a
member of the PBA
[Music]
family FWD is all about passion and
we're here to protect our customers no
matter what life may throw at them doing
anything that they feel that they want
to do the passion following the passions
of their life we're a new type of
insurance company with a vision to
change the way that people feel about
insurance and we believe that this
exciting partnership with the PBA is a
great platform for us to show Filipinos
that we are an insurer that dares to be
different we look forward to a long and
successful partnership together so that
we can all get ready to
[Music]
live